https://www.se-fi.com/privacy-policy

Section I – General Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting the StoneEagle F&I website. Please note that this General Privacy Policy describes our overall privacy practices for the website. Section II is our privacy policy for nonpublic personal information used in the provision of our services.
Please note that in the event we amend the Privacy Policy, posting the amended version will serve as notice to you of that change and the policy will note its effective date.
Some information collected is non-identifying. For example, although our website servers collect information about a user’s internet protocol address, our server is not able to automatically associate that information with a particular user. We may collect non-identifying information associated with that address, such as the time and date of a visit, the originating domain name, the browser type, and the particular pages or products viewed on the website.
The website may utilize a “cookie.” A “cookie” is a small text file that a website can place on your computer’s hard drive or on your mobile device’s memory in order to collect information about your activities on our website. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you have the option to change your browser to decline them. We use cookies on certain areas of our website, but these cookies are not used to identify anonymous website visitors. Our cookies enable you to proceed smoothly through our website and enable us to know whether you’ve used our website before to eliminate some steps that are directed to new visitors. Similarly, a cookie may be placed by our third-party advertising companies. These companies may use aggregated statistics about your use of our website and third party websites in order to determine your age and gender, which may be used to provide you with advertisements about goods and services that you may be interested in. The information they collect does not include your personal information.
Image tags work in conjunction with cookies. An image tag, also referred to as a clear GIF or web beacon, is a small image file that may be located on select areas of our website.
At this time, we have contracted with Google to collect information about how users navigate our website.
With respect to unrelated, third party web sites, such as third party online retailers, advertisers, or unrelated sites that we may happen to link to, or web sites that link to our website, those third parties may collect personal information directly from you. The information policies and practices of these unrelated parties are not covered by this privacy policy. We do not control the privacy policies of third parties even if we may provide hyperlinks or other access to their web sites. We are not responsible or liable for their independent policies and practices. Please review their privacy policies and practices. It is your responsibility to review them and decide if you are satisfied with their protections.
We receive certain personally identifying information that is delivered to us by the dealership management systems, menu presentation systems and/or administration systems.
We take commercially reasonable steps to protect the information we collect online. However, as effective as these measures are, no security system is impenetrable. We do not provide an absolute guarantee of the security of our information databases, nor do we guarantee that the information you may choose to supply will not be intercepted while you transmit it from your computer, over the internet, or along other third party networks, and to our systems. However, with respect to security: when we intend to transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information, such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server using, for example, Transport Layer Security or Secure Sockets Layer security.
We work with analytics companies to help us understand how our websites are being used, by how many users, for how long, and how frequently. Using analytics, we receive counts of the screens and features of our website that are used, the countries from which they are used, device language settings, demographics and interests information, including the types of devices, operating systems, browsers, addresses and wireless connections our users are using.
California Users: Your California Privacy Policy
For residents of California Only. The California Consumer Privacy Act requires certain businesses to disclose policies relating to the collection, storage, receipt of, and/or sharing of certain categories of customers' personal information with third-parties. These businesses are required to accept such requests from customers but are only required to honor two requests per calendar year. Businesses have forty-five (45) days to respond to each inquiry. Each inquiring customer will receive a detailed list of the information collected, received and/or stored, as well as an explanation of the categories of customer information shared and the names and addresses of the third-party businesses, if applicable.
*If you are a current StoneEagle F&I customer in California and you want to submit a request to us regarding your California rights, including requests to (i) access your personal information, (ii) have your personal information erased, or (iii) exercise any of the rights listed herein below, please click here or email us at privacy@se-fi.com.
*You may also call us at 855-937-8729
Section II–Privacy Notice for Personal Information
Facts: WHAT DOES STONEEAGLE F&I DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why
StoneEagle F&I operates as a software service provider to automobile dealerships, third-party administrators of vehicle services contracts and aftermarket and ancillary products, general agents and OEMs.  Our primary software platforms are our retail reporting for sales, finance and insurance and fixed operations, and Menu presentation software tools along with our administration systems that manage the complete life cycle of vehicle service contracts, aftermarket and ancillary products.  As a service provider, the information we collect is used by the parties noted above in managing dealer performance, presenting products to purchasers, and delivering contract data to the third-party administrators of the vehicle service contracts, aftermarket and ancillary products.
What
The types of personal information we collect depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Name
Address
Email Address
VIN
Phone Number
Birthday
Age
Gender
Loan Number
Customer Account Number with Lender
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?This notice is being provided on behalf of StoneEagle F&I
What we do
How does StoneEagle F&I protect my personal  information?To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does StoneEagle F&I receive your personal information?We receive your personal information from the Dealership Management System or from manual entry into one of our software platforms based on your transaction or exchange of information with a dealership when you purchase a vehicle or have your vehicle serviced, including but not limited to when you:
Apply for financing
Complete a cash deal
Purchase a car
Utilize a dealership service department for repairs or services
Apply for a lease
Give us your contact information
Your Employee Number or Name are in the dealership management system for our performance management services
Choose products during a Menu presentation or when a dealer employee enters your information into our portal which delivers the information to your respective product administration company
The rights of California consumers under the CCPA are detailed below:
California Consumer Rights
Right to Know/AccessUpon the direct request of a California consumer, up to two times per year, StoneEagle F&I will provide a description of and access to the pieces of personal information that our company has collected about you in the previous twelve (12) months.
Right to Be ForgottenUpon the direct request of a California consumer, StoneEagle F&I will work diligently to determine which software platform contains your information, and then directly or via instructions to our dealer or administrator partners delete, obfuscate and/or remove data about said individual.  Third-party administrators use the collected information to administer cancellations, claims and additional items on each customer contract, and deletion may have to be completed via obfuscation as per the applicable statutes.
Right to Opt OutStoneEagle F&I does not sell customer information, and as such, is not subject to the Opt Out requirements.  Should this change, StoneEagle F&I will update its Privacy Policy and the Opt Out requirements section.
Right to Be Free from DiscriminationStoneEagle F&I does not discriminate against a consumer because the consumer exercised any of the consumer’s rights under the CCPA, including, but not limited to, by:
Denying goods or services to the consumer.
Charging different prices or rates for goods or services, including through the use of discounts or other benefits or imposing penalties.
Providing a different level or quality of goods or services to the consumer.
Suggesting that the consumer will receive a different price or rate for goods or services or a different level or quality of goods or services
sales@se-fi.com
Corporate Office - Dallas: (855) 937-8729
1900 Jay Ell Dr.
